innovate1services.com 2017-01-09

# INNOVATE1 Services

**This Privacy Notice was last modified: August 12 2014**

It is the policy of INNOVATE1 Services to protect and preserve the privacy of its clients, users and customers and the confidentiality of the Information they provide, subject to conditions described below. To demonstrate our commitment to privacy we encourage all of our current and prospective users to read this Privacy Policy carefully before using this site and our services. By using this site ([www.innovate1services.com](http://www.innovate1services.com/) ) and the associated services, You acknowledge reading and accepting this Privacy Policy and all accompanied Terms of Use. INNOVATE1 Services reserves the right to expand and/or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. 

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to INNOVATE1 Services its parents and related entities, subsidiaries, whether or not wholly owned (“INNOVATE1 Services”) and specifically, it outlines the types of Information that INNOVATE1 Services gathers about You (“User”) while You are using the [https://www.innovate1services.com](https://www.innovate1services.com/) Website or any other website that links to or uses the INNOVATE1 Services Service now or in the future ("INNOVATE1 Services Website(s)"). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the INNOVATE1 Services Terms of Use. Your use of the INNOVATE1 Services Website and any personal Information You provide on the INNOVATE1 Services Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

During enrollment for INNOVATE1 Services, we require You to enter your personal Information. These may include your name, debit or credit card number, card verification number, card expiration number, address, telephone number and email address. For Providers, we require that You provide your bank account number and may require your personal address, business category, social security number and other Information concerning your Payment Transaction (‘Information”). This Information is stored within your INNOVATE1 Services account. 

Personally identifiable Information submitted via the INNOVATE1 Services website is used only for limited purposes. Information You submit may be used to respond to You, to create a personal profile, to facilitate further requests or inquiries, or to personalize your user experience on innovate1services.com. In addition, the webmasters may, where necessary, use your Information for various site-related tasks. Such Information will not otherwise be shared with third parties unless disclosed at the point of collection. Personally identifiable Information may be transmitted internationally to third parties for the purposes identified above. This may include transfer to countries without data protection rules similar to those in effect in your country of residence. By providing Information via the INNOVATE1 Services website, You are consenting to such transfers. Where necessary or desirable to comply with legal or regulatory obligations or requests, or for the purposes identified above, personally identifiable Information may be disclosed to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or third parties. INNOVATE1 Services also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable Information and/or non-personally identifiable Information that INNOVATE1 Services believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary in order to enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, assist government enforcement agencies, protect the security or integrity of the INNOVATE1 Services website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of INNOVATE1 Services, our Users or others. In all cases we will treat requests to access Information or change Information in accordance with applicable legal requirements. Please do not send us any personal data if You do not consent to the transfer of this Information as outlined above. 

We may obtain Information about You from third parties to protect You from fraud, financial misconduct, and to verify the Information You provided. 

We collect Information about every Payment Transaction carried out by You using the INNOVATE1 Services Service. These include but are not limited to transaction amount, description of the goods or services being provided by the Provider, names of the Provider and the Customer and the modes of payment employed. 

We may require Information about your service usage to enable us to validate your identity and thereby stall any fraudulent conduct. Such Information will only be used to prevent fraud. Any other use would require your expressed permission. 

We use cookies for browser identification every time You access an INNOVATE1 Services web page. This enables us to improve the quality of our service by saving your preferences and customizing your user experience. Cookies do not store any personal Information. All of the Information is entirely confidential and is never sold or seen outside of the company.

Our servers record Information sent by your browser each time You use INNOVATE1 Services. These logs may include your IP address, the browser type and language, the date and time of your request, your web requests and cookies that help identify your browser.

We may save emails and other communication sent by You to enable us to process your queries, respond to your requests, and improve our services.

We may present links in a format that will help us identify if they were followed or not. Using this Information can help us improve the quality of our search feature, provide quality services to You, carry out auditing, research and analysis for improving the quality of our services, facilitate the technical functionality of our network and develop new solutions. 

We take measures to ensure that the Information You provide is recorded accurately and completely and is stored securely. Information collected from/about Customers is used exclusively for the purpose of providing better service. It is never released to third parties except when expressly permitted by the customer. Any Information You provide is completely confidential and will be protected from unauthorized use.   
However, we may share your personal Information with individuals outside INNOVATE1 Services in the following situations:   

  * Credit/debit card transactions are processed through a third party. All Information is encrypted and is used only to complete the appropriate transactions.
  * To prevent or detect fraud or technical issues.
  * Where we have your consent and User has elected to optin for the sharing of any personal Information.
  * We provide such Information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal Information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such Information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such Information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of INNOVATE1 Services, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * We may share aggregated non-personally identifiable Information with third parties. If we do share this aggregated Information, we do not include personally identifiable Information without your explicit opt-in consent or in the limited circumstances described above. 
  * In the event that INNOVATE1 Services is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the Information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal Information is treated, transferred, or used.

You must keep your User/Private ID and Password confidential. If You do share this Information with a third party, they could obtain access to your account and all personal Information stored within. 

You will be able to update your payment Information by signing into your INNOVATE1 Services account and going to the appropriate page. In this page, You can change your address and method of payment. You can also see or print your previous transaction history. 

However, to facilitate our auditing and reporting functions, and also to guard against fraud, the Information will be saved to our systems but will not be shared with anybody.

Note that disabling your INNOVATE1 Services transaction history functionality does not close your INNOVATE1 Services account.

By accessing this site and using its services, You unconditionally agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. You agree to comply with the terms that govern the use of this site and its services and that also govern all Information provided by You and other users of innovate1services.com. If You do not agree to all or any of the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site.
